

+33 6 32 79 98 59

colin.noiret@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/colin-noiret

github.com/Colingue

## **EXPERTISE**

**Mastered languages:** JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, HTML, CSS

Frameworks / Libraries : Next.js, React, NodeJS, React Native, Express, Jest

**Skills:** PostgreSQL, API REST, CI/CD, Unit Testing, Project management

#### Tools:

Cloud: Azure, Git, GitHub, Docker, PowerBl, Jira, Notion, Asana

Design: Photoshop, Canva, Figma

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Problem-Solving Team work Autonomous Persistent

## **LANGUAGES**

French (Native)
English (Intermediate)

#### **REFERENCES**

## Jérôme Descubes

Groupe Save | IT Manager

Phone: +33 6 27 30 14 60

Email: jdescubes@save-france.fr

#### **HOBBIES**

Guitar Bodybuilding, Tennis Gardening

# **COLIN NOIRET**

## **WEB DEVELOPER**

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a recent IT Master's graduate with 3 years of experience in frontend and mobile development. Passionate about web development, I want to work abroad to face new professional challenges. Rigorous, proactive, and dedicated, I am confident that my skills will positively contribute to your company.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Web and mobile developer

Groupe Save | Bordeaux | Oct 2022 - Present

- Enhanced front-end development of a web application
- Contributed to the development of a React Native mobile app
- Developed client extranet as lead developer
- Implemented cloud solutions via Azure
- · Code review
- · Set up and led daily stand-ups.

## Co-founder, student entrepreneur

Meetmapper | Business incubator | Oct 2022 - Present

- Front-end development with integration of interactive mapping
- Developed secure and reliable back-end APIs
- Deployment to servers, CI/CD and DevOps practices
- Managed team, project progress, and task assignments.
- · Analyse the market and define a product

## Web developer

Webforme | Bordeaux | Aug 2021 - Sept 2022

- · Developing the front and back offices of e-commerce websites
- Custom web tool development for Prestashop
- Identified needs and defined solutions with clients.

## Web developer

IUT UCA | Montluçon | Avril 2021 - Juin 2021

- Web application development for equipment booking.
- Website prototyping

## **EDUCATION**

MSc Business & Technology Manager (apprenticeship)

Epitech | 2022 - 2024

Professional License in Web Applications (apprenticeship)

University of Bordeaux | 2021 - 2022